Navin Hariharan

Tamil Nadu, India



navin@cyberhakz.com



+917305574234



linkedin.com/in/navin-hariharan

Summary

I have over 6 years of experience in the field of Cybersecurity. Currently, I hold the position of the Chief Executive Officer at CyberHakz Pvt. Ltd and Director of Alfa Global Wealth Advisors Pvt. Ltd. I Also hold powerful positions in almost 20 other Companies/Communities/Organisations!

If you catch me outside of work, I'm an adventurous traveller - 14 countries and counting!

Competencies: Python, Javascript, Java, C, C++, Bash, SQL, HTML, PHP

CERTIFIED ETHICAL HACKER

I also like meeting new people over a cup of coffee. Feel free to reach out at one of the following:-Instagram:- @navin_hariharan Whatsapp:- +917305574234 (Avoid Calling).

Experience



Director

ALFA GLOBAL WEALTH ADVISORS

Mar 2021 - Present (3 months +)

We understand that good wealth management takes place over many years and we, therefore, look to build long-term relationships with our clients. Our clients have absolute trust in us and we will work with many of our clients over the course of their lifetimes into retirement and beyond!



Founder/CEO

Cyberhakz

Sep 2018 - Present (2 years 9 months +)

Education



Chennai Institute of Technology

Undergoing, Computer Science 2020 - 2024

Licenses & Certifications

Certified Ethical Hacker - EC-Council

Issued May 2021 - Expires May 2024 ECC8513964720

Skills

Software Coding • Software Development • Computer Science • Ethical Hacking • cyberpolice • Python (Programming Language) • Bash • C (Programming Language)

Honors & Awards

CYBERSECURITY SUMMER INTERNSHIP - GURUGRAM POLICE
Jun 2020

AWARNESS CAMPAIGN - Sairam Institutions

CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPITATION - Kyrion Technologies Feb 2020

CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPITATION - CybHER Sep 2020

CERTIFICATE OF APPRECIATION - SHERLOCK INSTITUTE OF FORENSIC SCIENCE Sep 2020